Susan Caperna Lloyd collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 17: India
  - Jaipur Amber Palace, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-7, 21-30, 33-37, Elephant rides at Amber Palace outside Jaipur; 8-10, 39-43, Hall of Private Audience at Amber Palace outside Jaipur; 11-12, The great wall surrounding Jal Mahal Palace is the third largest wall in the world; 13, 19-20, 46-47, Jal Mahal Palace on Sagar Lake near Jaipur. It was built in the 1799 in Rajput style by Maharaja Sawai Pratap Singh and hosted royal duck shooting parties but now the bottom floors are underwater and the palace is closed to the public; 14, 17-18, Walls of Amber Palace; 15, 44, Gardens of Amber Palace near Jaipur; 16, 45, Woman in traditional sari in Amber Palace gardens; 31, Plaque at Siladevi Temple at Amber Palace outside Jaipur. It commemorates how in the sixteenth century Maharaja Man Singh brought a stone image of the Hindu deity Kali from the sea near Kolkata to Jaipur. Kali brought the Maharaja victory in battle and then became known in Jaipur as Shila Devi; 32, Plaque explaining the Hall of Public Audience at Amber Palace; 38, Royal garden retreat on pond at Amber Palace.; 47 still image files (jpg)
  - Diu, Gujarat, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-3, 7, 10-11, 43-47, 50, 77, 81-82, Diu Fort on the island of Diu. It was built by the Portuguese in the sixteenth century when they colonized this area on the west coast of India; 4, Susan Lloyd at Diu Fort; 5-6, 8-9, 12-14, 48, Visitors at Diu Fort; 15-18, Wandering cow; 19, Police Complaint Authority sign; 20-22, 51-52, 55-57, Women carry rocks to and from construction sites using traditional carrying rings on their heads; 23, 87-90, Untitled; 24, 27-28, 67, Saint Thomas Church; 25, Diu Museum sign; 26, Sculpted snake on bottle in Diu Museum; 29-34, 38-40, Diu architecture; 35, 70, 83-86, Goats on the street; 36, Setting sun over Indian Ocean from Diu beach; 37, 78, Cobra sign of Shiva on Diu Hindu temple; 41-42, Diu Fort wall detail with cloth washing room sign; 49, 79-80, Bas relief of St. James on horseback at Diu Fort; 53, Diu traditional fishing boat at anchor; 54, 64, Workers repairing traditional fishing boat; 58-62, Traditional Diu fishing boats at low tide; 63, Traditional Diu fishing boat and fishermen at low tide; 65, Ekta Travels bus ticket sign; 66, Saint Thomas Church inner stairway; 68, Ancient Hotel Santo Tomas sign and entrance; 69, Diu architectural fence; 71, Statue of Portuguese explorer Nuno da Cunho in Diu park; 72-74, Cows in busy Diu street; 75-76, 91-93, Clam diggers on Diu Island.; 93 still image files (jpg)
  - Diu Santos, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-2, Stone bas relief of Catholic saint at Diu Fort. The tradition of folk art santos saint statues was brought to Diu in Gujarat by the Catholic Portuguese colonizers in the eighteenth century; 3-4, Carved statue of Virgin Mary and Child in Santo Tomas Church. The statues were often carved by Indian carvers and resembled ancient Hindu statuary art; 5, Carved and painted statue of Virgin Mary with Indian facial characteristics in Santo Tomas Church; 6, Stone relief fragment of St. Michael in Santo Tomas Church; 7, 11, Saint statue with clothing fragment in Santo Tomas Church; 8, Carved saint statue (designed to be dressed in wig and clothing) in Santo Tomas Church; 9, Carved santo of St. Thomas in Santo Tomas Church; 10, Carved statue of Virgin Mary standing on moon and carved snake on bottle in Santo Tomas Church.; 11 still image files (jpg)
  - Varanasi Fire Ceremony, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-36, Fire ceremony called Aarti at Dasawahmeda Ghat in Varanasi. Fire is a link between this world and the spirit world in this daily purification at dusk which is offered to the Ganges River and the Hindu Lord Shiva.; 36 still image files (jpg)
  - Jaipur Galtaji Monkey Temple, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1, Phallic Shiva tower at Galtaji Temple. It is known as the Monkey Temple because of the presence of rhesus macaques and is a Hindu pilgrimage site outside Jaipur founded by aesthetics belonging to the Ramanuja sect of Hinduism; 2, 9, 33-35, 38-50, 52-58, 63-64, 77-82, 97, 99-100, Monkeys abound at Galtaji Temple; 3-4, 6, 8, 60-61, 83-89, 92, 98, Wandering cow at Galtaji Temple; 5, Pilgrims at Galtaji Temple; 7, 28, Galtaji Temple detail; 10-12, Galtaji Temple detail of mural depicting Rajput history; 13, 15, 19-23, 67-68, 94, Statue of Hanuman at Galtaji Temple. Hanuman is the Hindu monkey god; 14, Vendor with flower offerings at Galtaji temple; 16, 30-31, 36-37, 91, Galtaji temple view; 17-18, Niche inscriptions at Galtaji temple; 24, Altar to Hindu deity Hanuman at Galtaji Temple; 25, 29, 70-72, 75, Brahmin at Galtaji Temple; 26-27, 74, Statue of Hindu deity Ganesh at Galtaji Temple; 32, Galtaji Temple sacred waters; 51, Motorcycle pilgrims at Galtaji Temple; 59, Street scene below Galtaji Temple; 62, 90, Modern painting of monkey at Galtaji Temple; 65-66, 93, Shiva trident on floor of Galtaji Temple interior; 73, 95-96, Susan Lloyd's husband, Tom Lloyd, with Brahmin at Galtaji Temple; 76, Galtaji temple bas relief.; 100 still image files (jpg)
  - Ghandi Ashram in Ahmedabad, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-27, Ghandi's ashram in Ahmedabad displays his history when he lived there but it still operates as an ashram and sponsors the production of traditional khadi spun cotton.; 27 still image files (jpg)
  - Gulabo Sapera, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-15, 42-47, Gulabo Sapera dances at the birthday party of her daughter. Gulabo is a snake dancer and national treasure of India from the low-caste Kalibeliya people of western Rajasthan; 16-20, Susan Lloyd with Indian snake dancer Gulabo Sapera; 21-41, Gulabo Sapera at home in Jaipur; 48-51, Poster of Gulabo Sapera advertising her performance at 2014 Pushkar Camel Fair in Rajasthan; 52-68, Gulabo Sapera dancing at 2014 Pushkar Camel Fair in Rajasthan; 69, Gulabo Sapera comes on stage to dance at 2014 Pushkar Camel Fair; 70, Poster of Gulabo Sapera.; 70 still image files (jpg)
  - Dancing with Gulabo Sapera, Jaipur, India, 2014, afc2018064_dc006; Susan Lloyd and Lola Hyat (Marseille, France) dance with India's national treasure, Gulabo Sapera. Gulabo is a renowned snake dancer of the Sapera snake charming class in India. She is from Jaipur, Rajasthan, and Lloyd studied dance with her in her Jaipur studio where this footage was shot.; 2 moving image files (mov)
  - Darjeeling, India, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-2, 18-22, 34-35, 38, 40-43, 53-56, 63-66, View of Mount Kangchenjunga from Darjeeling. Kangchenjunga is the third highest peak in the world at 28.1k feet in elevation; 3, 24-33, Monkeys on Observatory Hill in Darjeeling; 4, 6, 11, 13, Shiva trident at Mahakal Temple in Darjeeling. It is a Hindu temple where both a Hindu priest and Buddhist lama perform religious ritual and offer prayers. It was built in 1782 and dedicated to Lord Shiva; 5, Monkey at Mahakal Temple in Darjeeling; 7, 9, Offerings being made at Mahakal Temple in Darjeeling; 8, Mahakal Temple in Darjeeling; 10, Buddhist monk Lama Tenzing at Mahakal Temple in Darjeeling; 12, View across Darjeeling valley from Mahakal Temple; 14, Statue of devotee on rooftop praying toward Mahakal Temple; 15-17, Monument to Sherpa Tenzing Norgay at Himalayan Mountaineering Institute. Tenzing Norgay successfully climbed Mount Everest with Edmund Hillary; 23, 47, Dogs resting on Darjeeling street; 36-37, Gandhi quote on sign on Observatory Hill in Darjeeling: Live today as if you are to die tomorrow; 39, 44-45, View of foothills around Kangchenjunga around Darjeeling; 46, Nepali woman on Observatory Hill in Darjeeling; 48m Chinese restaurant in Darjeeling; 49-50, Harrods Darjeeling tea estate; 51-52, Ganesh statue in roadside garden; 57-60, Buddhist monk Lama Tenzing from Mahakal Temple visits Susan Lloyd to show her the original Tibetan Book of the Dead kept in his monastery in Darjeeling.; 66 still image files (jpg)
  - Kolkata Pareshnath Jain Temple, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-3, 6-7, Entrance deity at Jain temple built by art connoisseur Ray Badridas Bahadur in 1867 in honor of the tenth Jain avatar Sri Sital Nath Ji; 4-5, 9-10, Jain temple; 8, Courtyard at Jain temple; 11-18, Caretaker at Jain temple.; 18 still image files (jpg)
  - Museums, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-3, Kolkata State Archeological Museum. Stone sculpture of Hindu deity Chamunda who is a form of the deity Kali, 1000 CE; 4, 6, 8, Kolkata State Archeological Museum. Stone sculpture of Hindu warrior deity Durga; 5, Kolkata State Archeological Museum. Stone sculpture of Hindu deity Parvati, 1000 CE; 7, Kolkata State Archeological Museum. Stone sculpture of Hindu deity Shiva; 9, Kolkata State Archeological Museum. Stone sculpture of Parvati is lotus position, 1000 CE; 10, Kolkata State Archeological Museum. Detail of stone sculpture of Kali stepping on Shiva; 11-12, Tourists on steps of Victoria Memorial Museum; 13, Albert hall Museum entrance; 14-16, Albert Hall Museum. Bronze casting of Hindu deity Shiva with entwined cobras; 17, Albert Hall Museum. Bas relief of Hindu deity Chamunda; 18, Albert Hall Museum. Description of Chamunda on museum wall; 19-20, 22; Albert Hall Museum. Sandstone door jamb depicting coiled snakes and Hindu deities, tenth or eleventh century CE; 21, Albert Hall Museum. Wall plaque describing sandstone door jamb; 23, Albert Hall Museum. Ivory statue of Shiva with the Ganges River flowing from his hair locks, 1200 CE; 24, Albert Hall Museum. Rajasthani traditional clothing display.; 24 still image files (jpg)
  - Shiva worship, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 378-391, Diu Fort Shiva altar; 392-394, Shiva and cobra symbols on Diu building in Gujarat; 395, Shiva trident at Galtaji Monkey Temple in Jaipur; 396, Painting of Hindu monkey god Hanuman attempting to save Rama's kidnapped wife Sita; 397, Altar at Galtaji Temple; 398-400, 408-410, 421-435, Graphics of Hindu deity Shiva on Varanasi ghats; 401-403, Sacred cows resting on Varanasi ghats; 404-407, Brahmin holding Shiva trident on Varanasi ghat; 411, Painting of Kali dancing on Shiva phallic symbol at Varanasi ghat; 412, 436-442, Altar to Hindu deity Kali at home and office of folk astrologer Dr. Srinivasan N. Shastry in Varanasi; 413, Detail of foot of Kali dancing on Shiva; 414, Altar to Hindu deity Shiva in Varanasi; 415-420, Phallic symbols of Hindu deity Shiva including cobra and trident on temple building in Diu Gujarat.; 64 still image files (jpg)
  - Indian laundry, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-28, 30-32, Laundry on ghats on the Ganges in Varanasi. In India laundry is often washed in the rivers and dried on the banks; 29, Cows on the banks of the Ganges.; 32 still image files (jpg)
  - Rajasthan Pushkar Camel Fair, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-4, 172-173, 186-187, Children at the Pushkar Camel Fair dress as Hindu deities such as Shiva. The nearby Pushkar Lake was legendarily made from a fallen Shiva teardrop; 5, Pushkar Camel Fair shoppers at the market; 6-15, 75-84, 86-106, 110-120, 169-171, Marwari horses are a rare breed associated with folklore and legends of the Maharajas and are brought to the Pushkar Camel Fair for breeding and for sale. With inward turning ears they have acute hearing and were warrior horses of the Maharaja; 16-36, 44-51, 61-69, 85, Herders bring camels and other livestock to barter and trade at the Pushkar Camel Fair; 37-43, Dancing Marwari horse competition; 52-60, Snake Charmer Sindhi Nath. He and his family camp at the Pushkar Camel Fair and are related to famed snake dancer Gulabo Sapera. His family is of the low caste Kalibeliya snake charmers although India has outlawed snake charming. This means the Kalibeliya would become sedentary and many endeavor to continue capturing cobras and their snake charming traditions; 70-74, 107-109, Longest mustache competition at annual Pushkar Camel Fair; 121-143, 174, 180-185, Pushkar Camel Fair folk dance; 144-147, Susan Lloyd with Sindi Nath snake charmer family; 148-153, 166, 168, Adornments on women of Sindi Nath family; 154-165, 167, Sindi Nath snake charmer family. They are Kalbeliya nomads of the low snake charmer class. They are experts with finding cobras and charming them; 175-179, Aarti ritual at Pushkar Camel Fair.; 187 still image files (jpg)
  - New Delhi Red Fort, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-13, The Red Fort in New Delhi became the capital of the Moghul Empire when it moved from Agra in the eighteenth century and contained the legendary Kohinoor Diamond.; 13 still image files (jpg)
  - River folklore, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-2, Bathing at Dakshineswar Ghat in Kolkata; 3-6, Bathing at Babu Ghat in Kolkata; 7-10, Hooghly River fishing culture; 12-15, 293-294, Pushkar Lake in Rajasthan is a pilgrimage site and believed to have been formed from the teardrop of the Hindu deity Shiva; 16-20, 22, 29-32, 34-41, 67-69, 90-91, 93, 119-120, 164-165, 179-190, 207-209, 215, 290-292, 301-305, 310-311, 313-329, 347-348, Boat traffic on the Ganges at Varanasi. Pilgrims come from afar to the sacred river to receive blessings from the waters as fishermen ply the river and transport goods; 21, 23-28, 33, 42-65, 72-88, 94-118, 121-163, 191-206, 210-211, 216-224, 226-228, 296-300, 306-309, 312, Pilgrims come from afar to the sacred waters of the Ganges at Varanasi to bathe and meditate. Some come to cremate family members and throw ashes into the river as others collect the water in puja pots to bring home to use for healing; 66, Sunset on Ganges River at Varanasi; 70-71, Meditating at a Varanasi ghat on the Ganges River; 89, Yoga Centre advertisement at Marsarovar Ghat on Ganges River in Varanasi; 92, Washing laundry in the Ganges River at Varanasi; 166-167, 170-171, 174-175, 330-346, Manikarnika cremation ghat in Varanasi; 168-169, 172-173, Wood used for cremations at Manikarnika ghat in Varanasi; 176-177, Cremation at Marnikarnika ghat at Varanasi on the Ganges; 178, Ruined boat on Varanasi ghat; 212-214, 282-289, Pilgrims float flowers in the sacred waters of the Ganges at Varanasi; 225, Susan Lloyd with women at Varanasi ghat; 229-281, A Hindu Brahmin in Varanasi conducts a puja ceremony for Susan Lloyd to help guide the souls of her dead family members into the afterlife; 295, Dasawamedha Ghat in Varanasi.; 348 still image files (jpg)
  - Sapera snake charmers, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-57, Snake charmer and cobra on streets of Jaipur.; 57 still image files (jpg)
  - Street life, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-6, 10, Jaipur tabla drummer; 7-9, Jaipur rooftops; 11-13, 32, 54-56, 71-72, 76, 88-90, 114, 136-137, 152-158, 170-174, 179-187, 195-205, 241-242, Saris and textiles; 14, 194, Pigs sleeping on Jaipur street; 15-17, Pigeons on rooftop; 18-20, 126, 142, 148, 150, 175-178, Rajasthan male dress; 21, 80, 115, 118, 122, 125, 147, 149, 151, 169, 218, 230-231, 239, 273, 291, People and places of India; 22, 28-29, 245-253, Jaipur Pink Palace architectural detail in Moghul style; 23-27, Jaipur street photography; 30, Susan Lloyd in Rajasthani dress; 31, 33, Jaipur motorcycles; 34-35, Kolkata sleeping dogs; 36, 81-82, Shoes left at Kolkata pandal during Kali Puja; 37-46, Kolkata (Bengali) male dress; 47-48, 64-70, 73-75, Devotees at street shrine during Kali Puja; 49-53, Street shrine at Kali Puja in Kolkata; 57, Kolkata drummer; 58-61, Gathering on Kolkata street to pay homage at shrine to Hindu deity Kali; 62-63, Woman in sari and bicycle; 77, Child in Kolkata street; 78, Women in saris; 79, Brahmin at street temple to Hindu deity Kali; 83-84, Building draped with lights during Kali Puja in Kolkata; 85-87, Puja ceremony in private home conducted by Brahmin during Kali Puja in Kolkata; 91-94, Communal meal in apartment building basement during Kali Puja in Kolkata; 95-96, Gypsy store sign on Kolkata street; 97-98, Sleeping Brahmins at Babu Ghat in Kolkata; 99-112, 145-146, 159-164, 207-208, 254-266, 269-272, 274-276, 278-283, In India cows are considered sacred and roam freely through the streets and public spaces; 113, 116-117, 119-121, 123-124, 127-131, 165-168, 192-193, 243, Pilgrims come to Pushkar Lake to meditate and bathe at the various ghats during the Pushkar Camel Fair. Folk legend says the lake was formed by the fallen tear of the Hindu deity Shiva; 132, Horse grazing alongside Pushkar Lake in Rajasthan; 133, Shiva trident at Pushkar Lake; 134, 244, Holy man at Pushkar Lake; 135, Brahmin at Pushkar Lake; 138-140, Holy man in contemplation by Pushkar Lake; 141, Hindu beads; 143, Rajasthan male attire and woman in sari at Pushkar Lake; 144, Women in saris at Dakshineswar Temple in Kolkata; 188-191, Monks carrying tin pails around Pushkar Lake; 206, Bicyclists and camels in the bazaar during the Pushkar Camel Fair in Rajasthan; 209-210, Camels walk through the bazaar during the Pushkar Camel Fair; 211-217, Aarti Fire Ceremony at Pushkar Lake ghat during Pushkar Camel Fair; 219-220, Wood for cremation at Varanasi ghat; 221, Puppies at Manikarnika Ghat in Varanasi; 222, 285-290, Brahmin at Manikarnika Ghat; 223-225, Kedar Ghat in Varanasi; 226-228, A Dom of the lowest caste and his child in Varanasi. The Dom are the people who cremate the dead; 229, A dog resting on the steps of a ghat in Varanasi; 232-233, The main marketplace in Agra; 234-237, Hotel Vimal Heritage in Moghul style; 238, Susan Lloyd at the Hotel Vimal Heritage; 240, Indian mujahideen wanted poster in train station; 267-268, Cord for sale in Agra market; 277, View from train window of couple with sleeping cot; 284, Puppies in bed of rags at Manikarnika Ghat; 292-295, A Brahmin conducts a healing puja ceremony at a Varanasi ghat; 296-300, Folk astrologer Dr. Srinivasan N. Shastry at home in Varanasi.; 300 still image files (jpg)
  - Agra, Taj Mahal, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-89, The Taj Mahal is an ivory marble mausoleum built by the Moghul emperor Shah Jahan in the 17th century to house the remains of his dead wife.; 89 still image files (jpg)
  - Northern India train travel, November 2014, afc2018064_dc001; 1-4, 8-19, 28-31, Train passengers and sleeping accommodations; 5-7, 20-22, 27, Country folk waiting by the tracks; 23-24, 26, Hennaed feet of woman on train to Varanasi; 25, Woman in red sari on train to Varanasi; 32, Train station wanted poster of drug criminals.; 32 still image files (jpg)
- Series 18: Other folk life projects
  - Subseries 1: Posters and signs
    - Political posters, graffiti, and signs, 1977-1998, AFC 2018/064: PH0741-PH0760; 20 color slides (35 mm); 741, Sidewalk chalk memorial to musician Robin Caston, Station Barbara, California; 742, Mexican boy in U.S. flag t-shirt, Guaymas, Mexico; 743, Demonstrators with posters against Marcos sequestration, Manila, Philippines; 744, Man in "People Power" t-shirt, Manila, Philippines; 745, Root growing on peeling tree graphic on wall, Rome, Italy; 746, "For English" peeling poster, London, England; 747, Defaced political poster (Teodora Valdez) on wall, Yautepec, Mexico; 748, "Boy" Herrera political poster on wall, Manila, Philippines; 749, Peeling music concert poster on wall, Rome, Italy; 750, Ice cream sign and pigeons, London, England; 751, Antique Appian Way sign, Terracina, Italy; 752, People's Power Coalition political posters on wall, Manila, Philippines; 753, Trading Post exterior and painted Navajo cornfield scene, Arizona; 754, "Abajo la oligarquia" Che Guevara sign on wall, Havana, Cuba; 755, Peeling posters on wall, Fiesta Republicana, London, England; 756, National Democratic Front wall poster, Manila, Philippines; 757, Man smoking and newspaper article about New Peoples Army, Manila, Philippines; 758, Political poster referring to "Philippine Guerilla," Manila, Philippines; 759, Ramon Revilla poster advert, Kapitan Pablo, Manila, Philippines; 760, National Democratic Front poster on wall, Manila, Philippines. (Box 5)
    - Billboards, posters, and signs, 1978-2003, AFC 2018/064: PH0721-PH0735; 15 color slides (35 mm); 721, Anarchist Book Fair sign, St. Andrews, Scotland; 722, "At any time" parking sign, St. Andrews, Scotland; 723, Princess Diana graffiti and flowers, Flamme de la Liberte, Paris, France; 724, Princess Diana graffiti about Angola land mines, Flamme de la Liberte, Paris, France; 725, Princess Diana tribute from Ireland, Flamme de la Liberte, Paris, France; 726, Princess Diana graffiti about Angola land mines, Flamme de la Liberte, Paris, Francis; 727, Collections mail box, St. Andrews, Scotland; 728, "Mind Your Head" subway sign, London, England; 729, Nene bird crossing sign near Kilauea Volcano, Hawaii; 730, Warren Brown/"Swan" matches poster, Hastings, England; 731, "Three minute maximum" phone call table, Quito, Ecuador; 732, Group of Black men and recliner billboard with white woman, Johannesburg, South Africa; 733, Defaced Evangelical minister poster, Nyssa, Oregon; 734, Percy Sledge and Mine Dance adverts, Johannesburg, South Africa; 735, News stand, Johannesburg, South Africa. (Box 4)
    - Billboards, posters, and signs, 1978-2003, AFC 2018/064: PH0736-PH0740; 5 color slides (35 mm); 736, Wet paint sign (in French), Paris, France; 737, "Stilla" decongestant sign on door, Trapani, Sicily; 738, Lottery advertisement, Swaziland, South Africa; 739, Sidewalk chalk memorial to musician Robin Caston, Station Barbara, California; 740, Gender specific job board, Johannesburg, South Africa. (Box 5)
  - Subseries 2: United States
    - Louisiana Cajuns, 1990, AFC 2018/064: SL-32-01; 29 black-and-white negatives (35 mm); Kodak 5052 (Box 23)
    - Cajun music, 1997, 1 folder (Box/folder 33/11)
    - Key West - ninety miles to Cuba, 1992, AFC 2018/064: SL-31-01; 27 black-and-white negatives (35 mm); Kodak 5053 (Box 23)
    - Hawaii, 1996, AFC 2018/064: SL-29-01; 36 black-and-white negatives (35 mm); Ilford (Box 23)
    - [Original housing from AFC 2018/064: SL-29, AFC 2018/064: SL-31, and AFC 2018/064: SL-32] (Box/folder 38/9)
    - Amish culture, Pennsylvania, October 2013, afc2018064_dc001; 1-4, 6-7, Tobacco drying in Amish shed in Lancaster county; 5, Amish home with laundry drying on front porch in accordance with their belief in non-mechanization and do not use washing machines; 8-10, Amish horses and buggies dominate the roads in Lancaster County Pennsylvania; 11-15, 17-19, 21-26, Amish corn fields are neat and well-kept; 16, 20, Amish clothes are washed by hand instead of by machine and are hung outside to dry; 27-28, Amish girl on bicycle.; 28 still image files (jpg)
    - Dobbin House, Pennsylvania, October 2013, afc2018064_dc001; 1-15, Legendary haunted Dobbin House and site of Underground Railroad.; 15 still image files (jpg)
    - Pennsylvania dog show, October 2013, afc2018064_dc001; 1-9, 11-93, Jim Rau dog show; 10, Dog brush with etching of dog and inscription.; 93 still image files (jpg)